Lian Songbai looks decent but is actually worthless.
ليان سونغباي يبدو لائقًا لكنه في الواقع لا قيمة له.
He has no real talent.
ليس لديه موهبة حقيقية.
Not long after he inherited the Lian family business,
لم يمض وقت طويل بعد أن ورث أعمال عائلة ليان،
he squandered it all.
لقد أهدر كل ذلك.
He came to the manor this time
لقد جاء إلى القصر هذه المرة
to inherit the manor and pay off debts.
وراثة العقار وسداد الديون.
The death of our senior brothers
وفاة اخواننا الكبار
was definitely his doing.
كان هذا من فعله بالتأكيد.
Master, I was wrong.
سيدي لقد كنت مخطئا.
I shouldn't have followed Lian Songbai out of vanity.
لا ينبغي لي أن أتبع ليان سونغباي من باب الغرور.
And I shouldn't have trusted Gao Li.
ولا ينبغي لي أن أثق في قاو لي.
Master, you're all I have now.
سيدي، أنت كل ما أملك الآن.
Since you were young,
منذ أن كنت صغيرا،
the rules I taught you,
القواعد التي علمتك إياها،
do you still remember them?
هل لازلت تتذكرهم؟
Between master and disciple,
بين المعلم والتلميذ،
there should be honesty.
ينبغي أن يكون هناك صدق.
You are mine.
أنت لى.
Wretch.
البائس.
Master, he's a beast.
سيدي، إنه وحش.
Master, I want to stay with you.
سيدي أريد البقاء معك.
I'll do anything you ask.
سأفعل أي شيء تطلبه.
Help me kill him.
ساعدني على قتله.
Husband.
زوج.
My face...
وجهي...
What's wrong, my wife?
ماذا بك يا زوجتي؟
Your face hurts, doesn't it?
وجهك يؤلمك، أليس كذلك؟
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
Your face used to
وجهك كان يستخدم
be worthy of the Lian family.
أن تكون جديرة بعائلة ليان.
But look at you now, so ugly.
لكن انظر إليك الآن، كم أنت قبيح.
You don't still think
أنت لا تزال لا تفكر
I'll treat you like I did before, do you?
سأعاملك كما فعلت من قبل، أليس كذلك؟
All I wanted was your face.
كل ما أردته هو وجهك.
I'll deal with you after I inherit the manor.
سأتعامل معك بعد أن أرث القصر.
Lian Songbai!
ليان سونجباي!
You shameless bitch!
يا لك من عاهرة وقحة!
You...
أنت...
Lin Xiaoran already knows about Bai Hua.
لين شياوران تعرف بالفعل عن باي هوا.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
But I can help you keep this secret.
ولكن بإمكاني مساعدتك في الحفاظ على هذا السر.
Master.
يتقن.
Don't believe this wretch's lies, Master.
لا تصدق أكاذيب هذا الوغد، يا سيدي.
Teng Rong and the others
تنج رونغ والآخرون
were surely killed by her for the manor.
لقد قُتلوا بالتأكيد من أجل القصر.
Master.
يتقن.
Lin Xiaoran.
لين شياوران.
Lin Xiaoran knows about Bai Hua.
يعرف لين شياوران أمر باي هوا.
Master.
يتقن.
Why are you so nervous?
لماذا أنت متوترة جداً؟
It's fine.
إنه بخير.
Just let me inherit the manor,
فقط دعني أرث القصر،
and I'll take care of him for you.
وسوف أعتني به من أجلك.
Bai Hua's body appeared at the birthday banquet.
ظهرت جثة باي هوا في حفل عيد الميلاد.
Then, the three dead all had black handprints on their shoulders.
ثم كان على أكتافهم علامات سوداء من أيدي القتلى الثلاثة.
Oh, I see.
أوه، أرى.
So the black handprint's purpose is...
لذا فإن الغرض من بصمة اليد السوداء هو...
You all...
أنتم جميعا...
Young hero Lin.
البطل الشاب لين.
Don't blame us.
لا تلومونا.
We warned you not to investigate.
لقد حذرناك من التحقيق.
Now you know too many secrets.
الآن أنت تعرف الكثير من الأسرار.
If you keep this up,
إذا واصلت هذا،
even your master won't spare you.
حتى سيدك لن يرحمك.
But the manor still needs an heir.
لكن القصر لا يزال بحاجة إلى وريث.
Now, I'm the only possible heir.
الآن، أنا الوريث الوحيد المحتمل.
Time to go.
حان وقت الذهاب.
Wait!
انتظر!
Don't you want to know who's really killing people?
ألا تريد أن تعرف من الذي يقتل الناس حقًا؟
If you kill me,
إذا قتلتني
you'll all die too.
سوف تموتون جميعا أيضا.
It doesn't matter anymore.
لم يعد الأمر يهم.
Master.
يتقن.
Are you satisfied now?
هل أنت راضي الآن؟
Satisfied.
راضي.
Only preserving the manor's reputation
فقط الحفاظ على سمعة القصر
for you, Master,
لك يا سيدي،
and for the Lian family,
ولعائلة ليان،
is truly beneficial.
هو مفيد حقا.
If we work together as master and disciple,
إذا عملنا معًا كمعلم وتلميذ،
we'll gain both fame and fortune.
سوف نحصل على الشهرة والثروة.
As for that bitch,
أما بالنسبة لتلك العاهرة،
Master, you can use her as you wish.
سيدي، يمكنك استخدامها كما تريد.
I wasn't wrong about you.
لم أكن مخطئا بشأنك.
Among all my disciples,
من بين جميع تلاميذي،
only you
أنت فقط
truly understand me.
افهمني حقا.
Master, you...
سيدي، أنت...
Fool.
أحمق.
If I agreed to your plan,
إذا وافقت على خطتك،
I'd probably be your first victim.
ربما أكون ضحيتك الأولى.
Go die with your fellow disciples.
اذهب ومت مع تلاميذك الآخرين.
My darling,
يا عزيزى،
go die.
اذهب للموت.
Old lecher.
فاسق عجوز.
Still not showing up at a time like this.
لا يزال لا يظهر في وقت كهذا.
I wonder if Lin Xiaoran has caused any trouble here.
أتساءل عما إذا كان لين شياوران قد تسبب في أي مشكلة هنا.
We'll find out soon.
سوف نعرف ذلك قريبا.
Officer Li, you've finally arrived.
الضابط لي، لقد وصلت أخيرا.
Please, come in.
من فضلك، ادخل.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
How has the manor been lately, Steward Wang?
كيف كان القصر في الآونة الأخيرة، سيد وانج؟
Officer Li, you came at an inconvenient time.
الضابط لي، لقد أتيت في وقت غير مناسب.
It's the manor master's birthday.
إنه عيد ميلاد سيد القصر.
He took several top disciples out traveling to enjoy the scenery.
أخذ عددًا من تلاميذه المتفوقين في رحلة للاستمتاع بالمناظر الطبيعية.
Only this old servant is left here to receive guests.
لم يبق هنا سوى هذا الخادم العجوز لاستقبال الضيوف.
I haven't visited the manor in years.
لم أقم بزيارة القصر منذ سنوات.
I didn't expect it to look so renewed.
لم أتوقع أن يبدو الأمر متجددًا إلى هذا الحد.
Late at night and early in the morning,
في وقت متأخر من الليل وفي الصباح الباكر،
it's the time for men to study.
لقد حان الوقت للرجال للدراسة.
The manor master's disciples have all made a name for themselves.
لقد صنع جميع تلاميذ صاحب القصر اسمًا لأنفسهم.
Even I feel how quickly time flies.
حتى أنني أشعر بمدى سرعة مرور الوقت.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
where is my friend Lin Xiaoran?
أين صديقي لين شياوران؟
Officer Li, you don't know?
الضابط لي، أنت لا تعرف؟
Your friend went traveling with the manor master.
لقد ذهب صديقك في رحلة مع صاحب القصر.
Didn't he tell you?
ألم يخبرك؟
From what I know of Lin Xiaoran,
من ما أعرفه عن لين شياوران،
he's not someone who breaks his word.
إنه ليس شخصًا ينقض كلمته.
He had an appointment with you.
لقد كان لديه موعد معك.
He wouldn't have gone traveling with them.
لم يكن ليسافر معهم.
Hmm.
همم.
Something's not right here.
هناك شيء غير صحيح هنا.
We need to go out and check.
نحن بحاجة للخروج والتحقق.
Officer Li, Lady Shen,
الضابط لي، السيدة شين،
I've prepared calming soup for you.
لقد أعددت لك حساءًا مهدئًا.
I'll put it in your room first.
سأضعه في غرفتك أولاً.
Drink it while it's still warm.
اشربه وهو دافئ.
Thank you, Steward Wang.
شكرا لك، ستيوارد وانج.
Hey.
يا.
After walking around,
بعد المشي حولها،
I feel like this manor
أشعر وكأن هذا القصر
still doesn't seem right.
لا يزال لا يبدو صحيحا.
Do you think Lin Xiaoran would really go traveling?
هل تعتقد أن لين شياوران ستذهب للسفر حقًا؟